<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Published</title>
    <description>Published materials</description>
    <link>http://ivanasetiawan.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://ivanasetiawan.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2014 21:36:22 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2014 21:36:22 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bird</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;You looked so sexy, real pretty with thick red lips &amp;amp; long brunette hair.&lt;br /&gt;
Cozy conversation..&lt;br /&gt;
Then he wondered about my girlfriend.&lt;br /&gt;
Then you asked how could I be single.&lt;br /&gt;
Then we made out.&lt;br /&gt;
Then I dumped us.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I loved your breasts, but I didn’t fancy your taste.&lt;br /&gt;
Run our function in a console, ‘us’ returns to null.&lt;br /&gt;
I am looking for an infinite number of specific prime numbers.  &lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2014 18:37:52 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://ivanasetiawan.com/jekyll/update/2014/12/26/bird.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ivanasetiawan.com/jekyll/update/2014/12/26/bird.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>CA</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;You taught me to be regret-less,&lt;br /&gt;
And I am trying my best to understand how,&lt;br /&gt;
When you are the main source of my regret.&lt;br /&gt;
It’s never your fault, nor mine. Just situations.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, I got diagnosed with autism.&lt;br /&gt;
That’s why my brain obsesses certain things like a maniac.&lt;br /&gt;
Something some close friends were already suspicious about.&lt;br /&gt;
All I wish is I knew it earlier, so I could notify you.&lt;br /&gt;
Who knows, maybe you could handle me better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I phoned you 3726 miles away, you sounded so you.&lt;br /&gt;
You seemed to be shocked that I still remember the story about your mom. &lt;br /&gt;
Of course I do, you’ve always been my main amuser.&lt;br /&gt;
I know I acted like a dumb fuck most of the time.&lt;br /&gt;
But all of the detail information you shared with me stored perfectly untouched in my brain.&lt;br /&gt;
It’s just that.. I cannot communicate how I feel fluently-aligned with my behaviour, &lt;br /&gt;
It seems like I push people away when I like them the most.&lt;br /&gt;
I don’t have to explain to you of course.. You experienced it yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2014 13:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://ivanasetiawan.com/lyric/2014/12/20/ca.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ivanasetiawan.com/lyric/2014/12/20/ca.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>lyric</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Next summer,</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Next summer might be fun. I think.&lt;br /&gt;
I am over you at least. I think.&lt;br /&gt;
OK. I promise I won’t expect, nor think.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Funny how I am back and forth and inside out about these three letters.&lt;br /&gt;
Is it still too funny for you that I was so crazy for you last year, the year before and the year before that?&lt;br /&gt;
One day before yesterday I still wondered if I could finally be good enough for anyone.&lt;br /&gt;
Not just anyone - I mean for you and you for me.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next summer might be fun..&lt;br /&gt;
I think..&lt;br /&gt;
I am over you at least.&lt;br /&gt;
Again, I promise I won’t expect, nor think.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I really hope it won’t be you, like last time at Westerpark.&lt;br /&gt;
I was so unhappy. Just in case you’re wondering. &lt;br /&gt;
I know you won’t. I just hope you would. &lt;br /&gt;
I lost my self slowly getting to know you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2013 18:37:52 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://ivanasetiawan.com/jekyll/update/2013/02/21/next-summer.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://ivanasetiawan.com/jekyll/update/2013/02/21/next-summer.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
